Matthew J. Pape

(262)290-1394

Plymouth, WI

matthewpape82@gmail.com

Summary

Very easy going happy go lucky person, dependable, hard working, love learning new and different things. I have worked in various jobs over the last 5 years and learned different jobs and skills. I am looking for a place i can grow with. And maybe be take on a leadership role.

Skills

- Operating a press
- inspection
- packing,
- trainer
- good communication
- fast learner

Experience

Press Operator

January 2018-Present

Ataco Steel Products,6809 Wi-60 Trunk Cedarburg WI 53012

- Operate a punch press for steel, inspect, and package parts
- Use Calipers and Depth Gages
- Metal Finish Parts with Belt Sanders and Sand Grinders
- Spot weldingparts
- Forklift Driving
- Fast Pace Work Environment

June 2014-January 2018

Injectec Inc, 451 N. Dekora Woods Blvd, Saukville, WI, 53080 - Press Operator

- Operate a injection molding press,inspect,and package parts
- Train New Employees
- Fast Pace Work Environment

March 2014-June 2014

Express Employment Professionals 11126 N.Cedarburg Rd, Mequon, WI 53092 - Temp

• Operate a injection molding press, fast pace work environment.

June 2012 - Febuary 2013

SpanCrete Inc, 2331 Spancrete Ln,Valders,Wi 54245 - Laborer

- Tore apart concrete beds, sand the floor and put finish coat on them
- Drove forklift,cut rebar,drove a bobcat
- Help build forms for concrete beds, puttied them, hand sanded

Education

August 1994 - 1997

Plymouth High School, Plymouth,WI